[
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "We discussed about the problem so thoroughly",
        "on the eve of the examination",
        "that I found it very easy to work it out",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "An Indian ship",
        "laden with merchandise",
        "got drowned in the Pacific Ocean.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "I could not put up in a hotel",
        "because the boarding and lodging charges",
        "were exorbitant.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "The Indian radio",
        "which was previously controlled by the British rulers",
        "is free now from the narrow vested interests.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "If I had known",
        "this yesterday",
        "I will have helped him.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "A lot of travel delay is caused",
        "due to the inefficiency and lack of good management",
        "on behalf of the railways.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "One of the members",
        "expressed doubt if",
        "the Minister was an atheist.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "I have got",
        "my M.Sc. degree",
        "in 1988.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "Having received your letter",
        "this morning, we are writing",
        "to thank you for the same.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "If you lend him a book",
        "he will lend it to some one else",
        "and never you will get it back.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "According to the Bible",
        "it is meek and humble",
        "who shall inherit the earth.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "Do the roses in your garden smell",
        "more sweetly",
        "than those in ours?",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "Block of Residential flats",
        "are coming up",
        "near our house.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "You can get",
        "all the information that you want",
        "in this book.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "The students were",
        "awaiting for",
        "the arrival of the chief guest.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "Sixty miles",
        "are",
        "a good distance.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "They have been",
        "very close friends",
        "until they quarreled.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "When the dentist came in",
        "my tooth was stopped aching",
        "out of fear that I might lose my tooth.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "It is the duty of every citizen to do his utmost",
        "to defend the hardly-won",
        "freedom of the country.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "No sooner did I open the door",
        "when the rain, heavy and stormy, rushed in",
        "making us shiver from head to foot",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "If a man diligently seeks to come into the contact",
        "with the best that has been thought and said in this world",
        "he will become simple and unselfish.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "You must",
        "remember me",
        "to post this letter.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": [
        "I shall certainly",
        "write you",
        "when I shall reach NewDelhi.",
        "No error."
      ],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": ["My father goes", "to the office", "five day week.", "No error."],
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": ["If she will be promoted", "she will get", "a higher salary.", "No error."],
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "(solve as per the direction given above)",
      "options": ["If I were him,", "I would have taught", "those cheats a lesson.", "No error."],
      "answer": "a"
    }
  ]
  